[
  {
    "QuestionID": 1,
    "QuestionText": "Environmental stressors can cause symptoms to flare up in koalas that have chlamydia.",
    "AnswerText": "True - Environmental stressors such as habitat loss, dogs, traffic, and noise pollution can cause an increase in symptoms for koalas with chlamydia. In some parts of Australia, chlamydia infection in koalas is as high as 90%",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 2,
    "QuestionText": "Koala joeys are both with no fur, no ears, and are blind.",
    "AnswerText": "True - Marsupial babies (joeys) are very underdeveloped at birth. Most of the development takes place in the pouch.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 3,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas hug trees to cool down.",
    "AnswerText": "True - Koalas are known to seek out certain species of trees with cooler trunk temperatures on hot days.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 4,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas have a cartilage plate under the skin on their rump, which allows them to sit comfortably on branches.",
    "AnswerText": "True - Koalas have a hard cartilage plate under the skin on their rumps. It even has a dent to help them balance in the trees.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 5,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas drink water every day, just like humans.",
    "AnswerText": "False – Koalas don’t often drink water unless the conditions are very hot and dry. They usually get most of the water they need from the eucalyptus leaves they eat.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 6,
    "QuestionText": "How many thumbs does a koala have on each hand?",
    "AnswerText": "True - Koalas have fingerprints that are similar to our own which help them firmly grip the branches.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 7,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas sleep so much because they become intoxicated from eating eucalyptus leaves.",
    "AnswerText": "False - Koalas do not become intoxicated from eucalyptus. They sleep so much because the leaf gives them very little energy.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 8,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas have unique footprints like humans.",
    "AnswerText": "Koalas have fingerprints that are similar to our own which help them firmly grip the branches.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 9,
    "QuestionText": "When they are first born a koala joey is the size of a _________.",
    "AnswerText": "Koala joeys are about 2cm at birth and weigh around half a gram (about the size of a jellybean).",
    "OptionA": "Grain of rice",
    "OptionB": "Jellybean",
    "OptionC": "Green bean",
    "OptionD": "Ping pong ball",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 10,
    "QuestionText": "One of the easiest ways to tell the sex of an adult koala is by looking at their:",
    "AnswerText": "The easiest way to identify the sex of an adult koala is to look at their chest. Male koalas have a dark brown scent gland in the middle of their chest and female koalas have a plain white chest.",
    "OptionA": "Ears",
    "OptionB": "Nose",
    "OptionC": "Chest",
    "OptionD": "Rump",
    "Answer": 3
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 11,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas can breed any month of the year.",
    "AnswerText": "False - Koalas are seasonal breeders. The breeding season in Southeast Queensland is from around September to March.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 12,
    "QuestionText": "How many grams of eucalyptus leaves do koalas eat on average a day?",
    "AnswerText": "On average koalas eat between 400 – 600 grams of leaf per day.",
    "OptionA": "5 – 10 grams",
    "OptionB": "400 – 600 grams",
    "OptionC": "5kg",
    "OptionD": "10kg",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 13,
    "QuestionText": "Koala joeys stay in their mother's pouch until they are around _____months old.",
    "AnswerText": "Koala joeys begin to spend time out of their mother’s pouch at around 6-months of age.",
    "OptionA": "6 months",
    "OptionB": "7 months",
    "OptionC": "8 months",
    "OptionD": "10 months",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 14,
    "QuestionText": "A baby koala is called a _________.",
    "AnswerText": "A baby koala is called a ‘joey’. This is the name for all baby marsupials.",
    "OptionA": "Pup",
    "OptionB": "Cub",
    "OptionC": "Puggle",
    "OptionD": "Joey",
    "Answer": 4
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 15,
    "QuestionText": "On average, an adult Northern koala can weigh between:",
    "AnswerText": "On average Northern koala females can weigh between 4 - 6.5kg. Northern male koalas weigh between 7 – 9kg. Southern koalas are heavier, weighing up to 14kg.",
    "OptionA": "4 – 9 kilograms",
    "OptionB": "20 – 30 kilograms",
    "OptionC": "2 – 7 kilograms",
    "OptionD": "15 – 20 kilograms",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 16,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas are a type of bear.",
    "AnswerText": "There is no such thing as a ‘koala bear’. While they are often called bears, koalas are marsupials, and their closest living relative is the wombat.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 17,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas usually give birth to _____ babies at a time.",
    "AnswerText": "1 – Koalas usually only give birth to one baby. Twin births are possible and have been reported, however these are very rare.",
    "OptionA": 10,
    "OptionB": 5,
    "OptionC": 2,
    "OptionD": 1,
    "Answer": 4
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 18,
    "QuestionText": "On average how many hours a day does a koala rest and sleep?",
    "AnswerText": "Koalas sleep and rest between 18 to 20 hours each day.",
    "OptionA": "1-5 hours",
    "OptionB": "24 hours",
    "OptionC": "8 – 10 hours",
    "OptionD": "18 – 20 hours",
    "Answer": 4
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 19,
    "QuestionText": "The average lifespan for a wild koala is:",
    "AnswerText": "The average lifespan for a wild koala is between 8-10 years. This can vary depending on food availability and threats in their environment.",
    "OptionA": "1 – 3 years",
    "OptionB": "8 – 10 years",
    "OptionC": "20 – 30 years",
    "OptionD": "15 – 20 years",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 20,
    "QuestionText": "Being hit by cars is one of the major threats to koalas.",
    "AnswerText": "True. While habitat loss and illness are the two biggest threats, injuries from being hit by cars and attacked by dogs are also major threats, particularly for our urban koalas.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 21,
    "QuestionText": "Which of the following could be signs that a koala is unwell?",
    "AnswerText": "All of the above answers could be a sign that a koala is unwell and in need of veterinary attention. If you see a koala showing these symptoms, you should call 1 300 ANIMAL to report it.",
    "OptionA": "Very thin",
    "OptionB": "Red, weepy or crusty eyes",
    "OptionC": "A dirty, wet bottom",
    "OptionD": "All of the above",
    "Answer": 4
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 22,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas only hang out in eucalyptus trees.",
    "AnswerText": "False – Koalas will often shelter or rest in trees other than eucalyptus, especially on a hot day.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 23,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas only move around at night.",
    "AnswerText": "False. Koalas are most active during dawn and dusk, which are their main feeding times. They will also sometimes move around during the day, so it is always important to watch out for them when you are driving and be sure to always keep your dog on a lead when walking near bushland.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 2
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 24,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas live within a home range.",
    "AnswerText": "True. If your house is in a koala’s home range, you may see (or hear) it passing through occasionally. You should make your yard koala safe by planting food and shelter trees, keeping your pet secure and placing wildlife escapes on your fence and in your pool.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 25,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas make a deep grunting noise. What is it called?",
    "AnswerText": "The deep grunting noise made by koalas is called a ‘bellow’. This is most commonly heard during breeding season.",
    "OptionA": "Guffaw",
    "OptionB": "Honk",
    "OptionC": "Oink",
    "OptionD": "Bellow",
    "Answer": 4
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 26,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas have special bacteria in their gut to help them digest eucalyptus. They are not born with these; how do they get them?",
    "AnswerText": "Koala joeys get the bacteria they need to digest eucalyptus leaves by eating a special poo from their mother called ‘faecal pap’ around the time of emergence from the pouch.",
    "OptionA": "From their mother’s milk",
    "OptionB": "From the eucalyptus leaves",
    "OptionC": "Passed through the mother’s saliva",
    "OptionD": "By eating their mother’s poo",
    "Answer": 4
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": 27,
    "QuestionText": "Koalas are endangered in Queensland.",
    "AnswerText": "True – As of February 2022, the Australian Government has declared the koala an endangered species in Queensland, New South Wales and the Australian Capital Territory.",
    "OptionA": true,
    "OptionB": false,
    "OptionC": "",
    "OptionD": "",
    "Answer": 1
  }
]